{
    "Questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who is most likely to name their variable 'Pizza'?",
        "answers": ["David", "Sean", "Eni", "Adam"],
        "correctanswer": "David"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who went to nursing school?",
        "answers": ["Shiraf", "Eni", "Laura", "Marcus"],
        "correctanswer": "Eni"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who owns a sweathshirt that says KALE?",
        "answers": ["Laura", "Amy", "Brenna", "James"],
        "correctanswer": "Brenna"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Who starts questions with 'Real quick...?'",
        "answers": ["David", "Alex", "Eni", "James"],
        "correctanswer": "James"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who likes animae more than Adam?",
        "answers": ["Marcus", "Sean", "Brenna", "Shiraf"],
        "correctanswer": "Marcus"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who is learning Arabic?",
        "answers": ["Shiraf", "Laura", "Eni", "David"],
        "correctanswer": "Laura"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Who recently moved and lost their internet?",
        "answers": ["Marcus", "James", "Shiraf", "Amy"],
        "correctanswer": "Shiraf"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Who cost Alex money with bad (HORRIBLE!!!) stock advice?",
        "answers": ["David", "Amy", "Brenna", "Sean"],
        "correctanswer": "Sean"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who got kicked out of their partner's parents' house?",
        "answers": ["Adam", "Alex", "Laura", "Amy"],
        "correctanswer": "Adam"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Who asks too many questions?",
        "answers": ["Shiraf", "Alex", "James", "Marcus"],
        "correctanswer": "Alex"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Who got engaged in Freiburg, Germany?",
        "answer1": ["Eni", "Brenna", "Amy", "Shiraf"],
        "correctanswer": "Amy"
      }
    ]
}